[{"question": " the reactor&#146;s gonna blow in three seconds, we&#146;re never gonna make it!", "answer": " you&#146;ve got to get out of here! save yourself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " no! i won&#146;t leave you!", "answer": " don&#146;t worry about me, i&#146;m a robot! i&#146;m just a machine!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " no you&#146;re not! not to me!", "answer": "  oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i am extremely talented!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " yeah, you&#146;re great! okay, let&#146;s take it from&#133;", "answer": "  no, i mean i was really acting my ass off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " yeah, i thought i was pretty good too.", "answer": " oh yeah, you&#146;re solid. yeah, you&#146;re just no me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? i think that&#146;s enough for now. yeah. i don&#146;t want to be over rehearsed.", "answer": "  fine! i&#146;ll do it without you!  i don&#146;t need you or anybody else! i&#146;m gonna make it on my own!  you&#146;ll see!! you&#146;ll all see!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  so uh, what&#146;s this thing you&#146;re auditioning for?", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s a new tv show. yeah. i&#146;m up for the part of mac macaveli or &quot;mac.&quot; yeah, i&#146;m a detective and i solve crimes with the help of my robot partner. he&#146;s a, he&#146;s a computerized humanoid electronically enhanced secret enforcer or-or &quot;c.h.e.e.s.e.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " so mac and c.h.e.e.s.e.", "answer": " that&#146;s the title! yeah! y&#146;know they really lucked out that the initials spell cheese.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " that is lucky.", "answer": " huh&#151;wait so joey if you get this, you&#146;re gonna be like the star of your own tv show! i mean you&#146;ll be like the big cheese!  or the big mac&#151;hey! you love those!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " well, don&#146;t get your hopes up, because probably not gonna happen.", "answer": " now-now, why would you say that joseph?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " i mean come on you guys! my own tv show? i just don&#146;t know if i&#146;m good enough.", "answer": " i am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " joey, what are you talking about? you&#146;re a terrific actor.", "answer": " you really think so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " whoa, she's pretty.  joey: yeah, and oh she's really nice too. she taught me all about how to work the cameras, and smell-the-fart acting. rachel: i'm sorry, what? monica: what? ross: excuse me? joey: it's like, you got so many lines to learn so fast, that sometimes you need a minute to remember your next one. so while you're thinkin' of it, you take this big pause where you look all intense, you know, like this.  chandler: oh, ok.", "answer": "  there's my scene, there's my scene.  &quot;mrs. wallace, i'm dr. drake ramoray, your sister's neurosurgeon. i'm afraid the situation is much worse than we expected. your sister is suffering from a...&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  vell, eva, ve've done some excellent vork here, and i vould have to say, your pwoblem is qviiite clear.  all you want is a dingle, what you envy's a schwang, a thing through which you can tinkle, or play with, or simply let hang...  joey: i play al pacino's butt. all right? he goes into the shower, and then- i'm his butt.", "answer": "  oh my god. joey: c'mon, you guys. this is a real movie, and al pacino's in it, and that's big!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " oh no, it's terrific, it's- it's- y'know, you deserve this, after all your years of struggling, you've finally been able to crack your way into show business.", "answer": " okay, okay, fine! make jokes, i don't care! this is a big break for me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " all right well, i&#146;m outta here. wish me luck.", "answer": "   gooood luck! gooood luck! we all wish you good luuuuuuuuck!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " it&#146;s your turn.", "answer": " oh, are we playing this?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey! how&#146;d the audition go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " terrible! i messed up every line! i shouldn&#146;t even be an actor!", "answer": " wait a minute, are you doing that thing where you pretend it didn&#146;t go well but it really did go well?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yeah, did i fool ya?", "answer": " totally!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " so it did go well.", "answer": " oh, it went amazingly well!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " great!", "answer": " oh that&#146;s great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah-yeah, it&#146;s down to me and two other guys.", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " and i know both of them, they&#146;re really good. one of them is the guy from those allergy commercials who&#146;s always getting chased by those big flowers&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh-oh, what are you doing?", "answer": "  what am i doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i&#146;m just so nervous! y&#146;know? the callback isn&#146;t until tomorrow at five. i feel like my head is going to explode!", "answer": " well, it is overdue.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " look, don&#146;t worry. okay? you&#146;re gonna be fine.", "answer": " there&#146;s just so much pressure. i mean no offense, but what you guys do is very different. i don&#146;t know if you&#146;d understand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " you ate my sandwich?", "answer": " it was a simple mistake. it could happen to anyone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  oh-oh really?", "answer": " now-now calm down. come look in my office, some of it my still be in the trash.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": " well, it was quite large. i-i-i-i-i had to throw most of it away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  ahh! aren&#146;t you dressed yet?", "answer": "  am i naked again?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " we&#146;re supposed to meet my parents in 15 minutes.", "answer": " yeah okay, i was just talking to the guys. just look at them i mean, is it okay if they come visit?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " wh?! what about my allergies?!", "answer": " oh right, your allergies.  all her, she hates you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " yes!! ha-ha!! all right! hey! how cool would it be if you could watch like a real life-sized version of this? huh? i mean how crazy would that be?", "answer": " as crazy as soccer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " you mean you didn&#146;t get it from this?", "answer": " the allergy guy got the part! thanks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " well, maybe we can fix it y&#146;know? maybe we can send him some-some big-big flowers and scare him!", "answer": " how could you do this to me chandler?! this part could&#146;ve turned my whole career around!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i messed up. okay? i&#146;m sorry, i really messed up.", "answer": " hey, you don&#146;t even live here anymore! what are you doing answering my phone? i have my machine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " look, i&#146;m not saying that you should magically forgive me! but you&#146;re not perfect! you&#146;ve made some errors in judgment too!", "answer": " name one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  what happened?!!", "answer": "  awww, man! he promised he wouldn&#146;t take the chairs!! chandler: what the hell happened?!! how were you locked in?!! and where the hell is all of our stuff?!! joey: well, this guy came by to look at the unit and-and he said he didn&#146;t think big enough to fit a grown man! chandler: so--you got in voluntarily?! joey: i was tryin&#146; to make a sale!! oh, man, if i ever run into that guy again, do you know what i&#146;m gonna do? chandler: bend over?!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " ok, now, remember, no trading. you get the pretty one, i get the mess.", "answer": " hi, joey.  well well, look what you brought.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " ...and what did you bring?", "answer": " she's checking the coats. joey, i'm gonna go wash the cab smell off my hands. will you get me a white zinfandel, and a glass of red for janice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " janice?!", "answer": " oh.... my.... god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " joey's tailor...took advantage of me.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " no way! i've been going to the guy for 12 years.", "answer": " oh come on! he said he was going to do my inseam, and he ran his hand up my leg, and then, there was definite...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " cupping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " that's how they do pants! ross, will you tell him? isn't that how they measure pants?", "answer": " yes, yes it is. in prison!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe i did this! what an idiot!", "answer": " oh, stop beating yourself up! people make mistakes! these things happen! there aren&#146;t any message you&#146;ve forgotten to give me are there?  apparently you&#146;re not very good at it! i&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " do you think he&#146;ll ever forgive me?", "answer": " of course he will! but chandler the most important thing is you forgive yourself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? i-i kinda have.", "answer": " already? that&#146;s pretty bad what you did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? he will forgive you. and i like to bring a pad with me when i go answer the phone just in case&#133;  okay&#133;", "answer": " you didn&#146;t see how mad he was, y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " it took two people to break up this relationship!!", "answer": " yeah! you and that girl from that copy place, which yesterday you took full responsibility for!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t know what i was taking full responsibility for! okay?! i didn&#146;t finish the whole letter!", "answer": " what?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " i fell asleep!", "answer": "  you fell asleep?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " it was 5:30 in the morning, and you had rambled on for 18 pages. front and back!!   oh-oh-oh, and by the way, y-o-u-apostrophe-r-e means &#145;you are,&#146; y-o-u-r means &#145;your!&#146;", "answer": " y'know i can&#146;t believe i even thought about getting back together again! we are so over!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  fine by me!! (he opens the door and traps chandler behind", "answer": " and hey! just so you know, it&#146;s not that common! it doesn&#146;t happen to every guy! and it is a big deal!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " you had no right to go out with him.", "answer": " that is the most ridiculous...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " you sold me out.", "answer": " i did not sell you out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yes you did. you absolutely sold me...", "answer": " would you let me talk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " did you just flick me?", "answer": " ok, well, you wouldn't let me finish and i was jus-  ow. that hurt", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " ok, now i'm gonna kick some ass.  monica and rachel: ow! ow! ow!", "answer": " i know! i know! i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " alright, now i will let go if you both stop.", "answer": " fine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " fine!", "answer": " there we go.you know what, if we were in prison, you guys would be, like, my bitches.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay, buddy-boy. here it is. you hide my clothes, i'm wearing everything you own.", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " please tell me you got the message!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " what message?", "answer": " the actor playing mac couldn&#146;t do it, they needed to see you at 2 o&#146;clock.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " what?! it&#146;s 6 o&#146;clock!", "answer": " du-du-i wrote it, i wrote it on the board! i wrote it on the board, then i went all over new york city looking for ya! i went to ross&#146;s! i went to the coffeehouse! i went to any place that they made sandwiches!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe this chandler!", "answer": " sorry! i-i-i don&#146;t know what to say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well you-you-you-you might say congratulations! i saw the board! i went to the audition! i got the part!!", "answer": "  is that supposed to be funny! i was really worried over here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " oh, well i&#146;m uh&#133;", "answer": " y&#146;know, sometimes that fake out thing is just mean!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh wow! okay man, i&#146;m sorry. i did not mean to make you feel bad.", "answer": " well that&#146;s good. because you didn&#146;t! and i&#146;m incredibly happy for ya!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": "  that&#146;s mean! you really had me going there!", "answer": " oh, we could do this all day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah, you&#146;re right. okay look, listen, let&#146;s talk about what a huge star i&#146;m gonna be!", "answer": " you are gonna be a huge star! i&#146;m gonna hug ya!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " you hug me!", "answer": " all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " hey, do we do this too much?", "answer": " i think so. yeah, get off me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " come on c.h.e.e.s.e., i&#146;m not leaving without you! try routing your backup source through your primary cpu.", "answer": "  i can&#146;t! my circuits are fried! they&#146;re fried i tell you!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " that&#146;ll be a neat trick, when you&#146;re,  when you&#146;re dead!", "answer": " ross, you don&#146;t have to yell.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " there was just an explosion, okay? my hearing would be impaired.", "answer": " i thought you were excellent! in fact for a minute there i was like, &quot;ooh, where&#146;d ross go?&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " thank you! and i have to say that first scene when you meet mac&#133;", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh my god. i mean&#133;", "answer": " y&#146;know what? i think that&#146;s enough for today. thanks for your help!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  he&#146;s holding us back.", "answer": " totally.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}]